the following program is from NE t the
public television network
[Music]
[Applause]
ok cuddles glider and blue eyes it's
time to close down the factory the king
and queen are expecting us at the annual
festival in tum-tums Town Square boy I
hear Harry trot on the band they make
great music
[Applause]
[Music]
their Majesties the king and queen
[Applause]
go on dear remember your little speech
thank you welcome everyone to the annual
festival which we hold here in come come
to express our thanks for the wonderful
bounty of lollipops that the giant magic
lollipop makes possible above Jason's
good as those made here in TomTom the
water purified by the giant lollipop
they are without equal
cuddles glider and blue eyes are now
fetching the magic lollipop so that I
can dip it in the fountain to purify the
water that make our TomTom lollipop so
your niggly delicious
[Applause]
magic mirror on the wall bring me what I
Madden bad but what most of all the
magical lollipop from tons of the square
none to its power can compare but once I
have it in the sand I'll make the best
lollipops in the land
[Music]
careful dragons don't drop it
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
I can't fly away it's up to you blue
eyes just drop them petals do your thing
that'll keep me busy while I send a
message a lollipop to let him know where
we are
[Music]
boy
gimme a kiss get me my magic medallion
Cosmo and be quick about it
now little dragons you are under my
power
from this time forth and for every hour
you will see what I want you to see you
I want you to be one your majesty your
majesty
I know where they are blue eyes has just
sent a message bad Bloods got them at
Blood Castle lollipop
we must get cuddles glider and blue eyes
back at all costs my friends too well
it's all right there the lollipop dragon
will look after them yes lollipop take
the children with you and get the magic
lollipop back too if possible come on
gang let's hurry
[Music]
well now we lollipop that's the forest
of mirrors we have to pass through it to
get the Baron bad Bloods castle the
where the where the forest of mirrors
well secret false your secret fears will
seems real smiles and tears who's that I
don't like this that's the invisible
lady the spirit of the forest of mirrors
[Music]
hey now they'll disappear if you just
sing the old happy song you know the
truth don't you Harry
[Music]
Wow
and your head do too much time
[Music]
candy bars and slimy worms
Pop's and
[Music]
we have to have a nightlight I never go
to bed without a nightlight that's easy
just think of a candle they're easy see
well what happens if I fall asleep don't
think of it anymore
denied everyone
[Music]
that's blood castle Oh like
Mira um no all most deadly
middle-of-the-mall
i order thee without delay go destroy my
enemies on their way by all the power my
magic releases to this now Oh be broken
in pieces
do you think that I might miss - don't
threaten me with all your might or look
to me to fight
[Music]
oh my what do we do now look at those
silver Birds look look Oh silver Birds
they're gonna burn it down
[Music]
[Laughter]
you little fools see I have the magic
lollipop and now I can make the best
lollipops in the land a single one you
just wait you'll get yours
[Music]
you throw that nasty little boy I don't
know window shut him up for good yes yes
[Music]
[Applause]
take a deep breath lollipop take a very
quick okay
[Music]
[Applause]
you RAM the castle lollipop dragon
that's now last you'll ever see of
princess Gwen but if you do anything to
hurt one hair on our little princess
I'll destroy your castle
[Music]
[Applause]
you'll punish I swear by all the bad
blood in my fat body that you'll pay we
can't get out
the door's unlocked
[Music]
[Applause]
blue eyes okay again do your thing
I'll go first to see if it still works
here goes
[Music]
[Applause]
boss boss hurry up idiots we must get
them before they get back to the forest
of mirrors we've got to get the magic
lollypop back to tum tum
[Music]
let's move it friends
sedum I feed her
more out of bound
[Music]
and I get away boys Oh No
[Laughter]
we never get across
come on everybody think of a bridge that
only works in the fast of nerves Gwen
did you say bridge
[Music]
okay everybody get across to the other
side
[Music]
[Applause]
we're safe now he'll never come in here
oh wow
[Music]
come on Cosmo will catch up
come with me not me baron uh-uh
Cosmo the cunning indeed you call me
what you want baron but my mama didn't
raise no fool you never know what will
happen to you in a forest of mirrors
it's the Baron he's coming in after us
wider you're gonna have to fly us out of
here come on everybody let's start
running and then we'll all hop on
lollipop
[Music]
I'll get you I'll get you
here
[Applause]
see what kind of truth you can get your
head and body back one day
[Music]
[Applause]
man am I glad to get away from that
place
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank You lollypop dragon and now
everybody cuddles
glider and blue eyes will give me the
magic lollipop that they rescued from
the clutches of the miserable of Balan
so I can water that makes dum dum
lollipops the best in the whole world
[Applause]
[Music]
nice work Harry couples Louise invited
you couldn't have done without you
I love you
we love you
[Music]
gay dragon
[Applause]
we'll be friends forever each and every
day
friend is someone you can trust
[Music]
it's great
as wonderful as you will be
[Music]
we'll be fresh
like you
[Music]
where they
[Applause]
[Music]
a little right right
perfect
we're all set for the annual lollipop
factory Christmas party
[Applause]
[Music]
enos musician
[Applause]
speech time oh my god factory workers
Merry Christmas Merry Christmas your
majesty to celebrate this joyous season
and thank you all for your fine work in
producing art tum tum lollipops the most
delicious lollipops in the world we
bring you Christmas presents and up in
our Christmas cheer
[Music]
cuddles liner and blue now assist
princess Quinn and Prince hubert as they
give out these small tokens of our
heartfelt gratitude
[Music]
ain't all this Christmas spirit it makes
my blood boil it's just a me boss like
they don't have a trouble in the world
fools they think just because it's
Christmastime but evil takes a holiday
[Music]
party change us he does something small
keep our evil
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah yeah
[Music]
in honor of the season a great Christmas
race will be run anyone may enter the
winners will receive the greatest honor
in the land the me pops
manufactured in their likenesses and in
the flavor of their choice to be given
to Santa Claus for distribution to all
the children of the world on Christmas
Day just imagine yeah a chocolate
marshmallow dragon berry pops what a
wonderful idea
you feeling okay plus it sounds awful
nice to me idiot
it gives me bad and bad blood the
perfect opportunity to ruin Christmas
not only TomTom but all over the world
[Music]
will your boss
those are just spiders they can't hurt
us
[Laughter]
[Music]
we got
Hey
[Music]
Oh
best to win
lunch
[Music]
we
every trick in a book
[Music]
how can I use you can't force up with
all these beautiful tiny tricks idiot
[Music]
baby Harry
am I ever I can already taste that hairy
troll I'm real lollipop remember you're
racing for the commemorative lollipop
which will be given to all the children
of the world in your favorite flavor on
Christmas Day
all the races not the line get ready
Oh No
well as I recall the Kings Proclamation
[Music]
unless the good people are TomTom ONE to
cheat I'm in the race solder beatable
I'm gonna win this foolish little
competition and that Christmas lollipop
will have my face on it and you what my
favorite flavor is
this is a disaster
how can we face center with Ferrand bad
blood lollipops for Christmas and in
such a horrible flavor it'll ruin
Christmas again I can't do that Hubert
much as I hate to admit it the Barons
got as much right to race us anybody
else here even if he is a bad blood
those are the rules and we've got a
right to beat him fair and square we are
going to do it we are going to win this
race pops right everybody
[Music]
good always giving our best is always
good enough such touching sentiments
let's right
[Music]
[Applause]
it's the
Phil can you pause that's him
the handle now you idiot
[Music]
[Laughter]
got a wind got a wind got a win/win/win
[Music]
[Applause]
you
[Music]
this is like a jack for Phil Krom some
speed Monty or we'll never catch up
we're overloaded Harry this is as fast
as these tired horses can go
[Music]
when I say now now boss no idiots not
now when I say now did you say now boots
all give that to me
[Music]
[Applause]
make my day now
[Music]
bye boys see you at the finish line
[Applause]
[Music]
he's got a new team
[Applause]
[Music]
so you want to fight dirty Hey
[Applause]
[Music]
Oh cashews
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
give me great pleasure to present the
winners with this year's from the fruit
of Christmas lollipop
learning from dragon hairy troll new
eyes Knutson slider my own dear children
how proud I am of you all not just for
feeding barren bad blood in the great
Christmas race funny but more being
courageous enough to do your best and
try your hardest
Lord is far more than this beautiful
commemorative lollipop you have our
deepest gratitude for saving Christmas
when Santa Claus comes we shall be proud
to present him with enough of these
lollipops all the children
[Applause]
make all your dreams come
every girl
that's mine
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
[Applause]